<dashboard script="components/data/generateDiag.js,runPageScript.js,vendor/bootstrap/bootstrap.js,vendor/bootstrap-multiselect/bootstrap-multiselect.js" stylesheet="vendor/bootstrap/bootstrap.css,vendor/bootstrap-multiselect/bootstrap-multiselect.css">

  <label>Telco Use Cases Content</label>
  <row>
    <panel>
      <html>
 <hr class="essentialshr" />
        <div class="lineheight24px"> 
          <a href="#" class="dropdowntext" id="desc1_link">  <div class="arrow-right-big" id="desc1_arrow"></div>          
          <img id="iiconmainpage" src="/static/app/Splunk_Essentials_For_Telco/images/general_images/info-icon.png" /> How can you map this content to Splunk's Essentials for Telco Uses Cases Journey, and gain operational intelligence?</a>
        </div> 
        <div id="desc1Section" class="welcome-header maindesc">
          <h2>Introduction to Telco Use Cases</h2>
<p>Welcome to the Splunk Essentials for Telco Use Cases app! In this app, we have provided <b id="analyticCount">340</b> different examples of how Splunk’s analytics-driven approach for Telco Use Cases and monitoring that can be used throughout your journey. To help you along the way, each example is documented so you can understand how it works, how to use it, and the level of difficulty.</p>
<p>What’s an example, you ask? An example is a fully-usable piece of application logs, metrics or external reference data using Splunk’s capabilities. They can be used stand-alone or in conjunction with others, and in Splunk Enterprise (core) or with ITSI. We also map into the four stages that represent the Splunk Telco Use Cases Journey.</p>
<p>Each example includes sample data so that you can see what it does, after which you are encouraged to turn it loose on your own data! To help you better match the example to your environment, we have prerequisite checks and thorough documentation. You can save searches directly from this app to create an alert action in Splunk Enterprise.</p>
<p>We recommend that to start you determine which of the four stages best represents where your organization is leveled today with Splunk. Next, you can click Telco Use Cases Content and explore the examples associated with that stage in the journey. The filters allow you to hone in on precisely the use cases, areas, and data sources that are applicable. And in case you forget, each page has a tour in the upper right that will walk you through all of the functionality!</p>
<p> Please note that each example search starts with <b>|inputlookup ...|some time format function|...</b>. This is artificially done in this essentials app, so that you do not have to index any sample data. To use the examples for your environment, replace the inputlookup with the usual <b>index=... sourcetype=</b> with your normal time picking matching your data and field names.</p>
<p><b>DISCLAIMER</b><br></br>
Please check with your local government regulation to determine how you can use these use cases to determine credit worthiness for an individual or company. Splunk is not saying or implying that we can help determine risk. Fraud use case examples of possible fraud detection are not a guarantee that fraud will be found. Use of these use cases is just an example of what is possible.</p>
          <h2>Financial Services Industy Use Cases Journey</h2>
          <div style="width:100%; padding-bottom: 25px;" class="column stagetablediv">
    <table id="stagetable">
      <tr>
        <td>
         <img src="/static/app/Splunk_Essentials_For_Telco/images/general_images/oimap.png"></img>
        </td>
      </tr>
    </table>
  </div>
        </div>
        <hr style="border: 1px solid darkgray;" />


        <div id="journeyContainer">
          <h2 style="float: left;">Filter Examples</h2>
          <div id="AnalyticCount"><b id="totalNum">241</b> Total   |   <b id="filterNum">241</b> Filtered
            <div style="padding-right: 25px; float:left" id="selectFilterLink"><a href="#">Select Filters</a></div>
            <div style="padding-left: 25px; float:right" id="defaultFilterLink"><a href="#">Default Filters</a></div>
            <div style="padding-left: 25px; float:right" id="resetFilterLink"><a href="#">X  Clear Filters</a></div>
          </div>
          <div id="Tour" style="float: right" class="tour"><a class="external drilldown-link" style="color: white;" href="contents?tour=contents-tour">Learn how to use this page</a></div>
          
          <div class="input input-dropdown splunk-view">
            <div id="rolePickerControl"></div>
          </div>
        </div>
        <div id="mainDisplay"></div>
      </html>
    </panel>
  </row>
  <row><panel><html><a href="#" id="downloadUseCaseIcon" onclick="return false;"><i class="icon-export" style="font-size: 16pt;" /> Export Content List </a></html></panel></row>

</dashboard>
