<dashboard script="runPageScript.js">
  <label>Introduction</label>
  <row>
   <panel> 
   <html>

 <table >
  <tbody>
    <tr>
      <td valign="top"> <h2>Introduction to the Telco Industry and Monitoring</h2></td>
	<td><div id="Tour" style="float: right" class="tour"><a class="external drilldown-link" style="color: white;" href="home?tour=home-tour">Intro Tour</a></div></td>
    </tr>
    <tr><td>
<p>Welcome to the Splunk Essentials for Telco app! In this app, we have provided <b id="analyticCount">340</b> different examples of how Splunk can be used to deliver Application Analytics, Telecommunications Compliance, and Detect Fraud for Content Service Providers / Telecommunications Companies! Splunk is your platform for data analytics--solving more than just IT and Security challenges. The goal of  this app is to show you new ways to use Splunk to address challenges specific to CSPs and Telco companies. It is hoped that these examples will show you the capabilities of Splunk applied to the Telco Industry. Since Splunk collects and indexes machine data in near real-time, most of the reports shown here can be run in near real-time providing you with a business advantage over other solutions. Because the analytics, fraud, and compliance departments at most institutions are different units, we have separated the examples here into their separate respective use cases to reflect that alignment.</p>
<p>What’s an example, you ask? An example is a fully-usable piece of application log, metrics or telemetry content using Splunk’s capabilities. They can be used stand-alone or in conjunction with others, and in Splunk Enterprise (core) or with Splunk IT Service Intelligence (ITSI), if it is a KPI metric. We also map these into four stages that represent the Splunk Telco Industry Journey.
</p>
<p>Each example provides insight on how it can be applied in your environment, how it works, the difficulty level and what data can be valuable.. After reviewing the examples, you are encouraged to apply the SPL in your own Splunk environment.
</p>
<p>We recommend you start by determining which of the four stages best represents your level of depth and breadth with Splunk. The filters allow you to hone in on precisely the use cases and , areas, that are applicable. And in case you forget, each page has a tour in the upper right that will walk you through all of the functionality!</p> 
      <p>Please note that each example search starts with <b><i>| inputlookup ... | some time format function |....</i></b> This is artificially done in this Essentials App, so that you do not have to index any sample data. To use the examples for your environment, replace the inputlookup with the usual index=... sourcetype= with your normal time picking matching your data and field names.</p>
      <p><b>DISCLAIMER</b></p>
<p>Please check with your local government regulation to determine how you can use these use cases to determine credit worthiness for an individual or company. Splunk is not saying or implying that we can help determine risk. Fraud use case examples of possible fraud detection are not a guarantee that fraud will be found. Use of these use cases is just an example of what is possible.</p>
      <p><b>Telco Use Cases Journey</b></p>
</td>
<td><img src="/static/app/Splunk_Essentials_For_Telco/images/general_images/logo.png" width="100%"></img></td>
</tr>
  </tbody>
</table>
     
   </html>
   </panel>
  </row>
  <row>
    <panel>
      <html>
        <div id="ListOfUseCases"></div>
      </html>
    </panel>
  </row>
</dashboard>
